One thing I really like about SageMaker is, especially,
我很喜欢 SageMaker 的一点是
with the built-in algorithms that are coming out,
其中有很多内置算法
there's a really big repository,
有一个非常庞大的 GitHub 代码库
GitHub repository that has like a Jupyter Notebook that walks through,
其中有步骤演示 Jupyter Notebook
and has some example data,
以及一些示例数据
and it walks through how to train and deploy each of these algorithms.
并且演示了如何训练和部署每个算法
I was wondering if you could speak to the decision to
你能解释下 除了参考文档之外
create this really big repository in addition to documentation.
创建这么庞大的代码库的初衷是什么吗？
Right. The idea behind the repository came,
好的创建代码库的推动因素是
our mission really is to put machine learning in the hands of every developer.
我们的使命是让每一位开发人员都能使用机器学习技术
So that's our mission. To do that we really thought
这就是我们的使命为了完成这一使命
about reorganizing the way we build technology around machine learning.
我们打算重新规划围绕机器学习开发技术的方式
So we built an entire staff that has three main layers.
我们将结构分成了三层
At the bottom layer,
在最底层
we make machine learning and deep learning frameworks available,
我们提供了机器学习和深度学习框架
though those are the TensorFlow,
包括 TensorFlow
the MXNet, the Phython,
MXNet Phython
[inaudible] , all these good programming languages of machine learning,
以及所有其他的精彩机器学习编程语言
that deep developers, data scientists,
深度学习开发人员 数据科学家
research scientists, would be very knowledgeable in,
和研究科学家非常熟悉这些语言
and they'll be a able to play around with that naturally.
他们能够轻松地尝试这些语言
But that's not for everyone.
但这并不适合所有人
So if you know exactly what to do,
如果你完全知道如何操作
if you can play with GPUs and recompile GPU libraries,
会使用 GPU 和重新编译 GPU 库
then, yes, you'll be very comfortable there.
那么在这一层级就如鱼得水
But then, at the middle layer we also built a lot of automation, like I said earlier,
在中间层级有很多自动化工具
for building, training, and deploying machine learning algorithms,
可以帮助构建 训练和部署机器学习算法
and that's really where SageMaker fits in.
SageMaker 就属于这样的层级
At the top layer there's a bunch of
在最顶层
applications services for computer vision and all this other stuff.
有很多计算机视觉等技术的应用服务
But because we want to talk about SageMaker for now, I'll focus on that.
但是我们现在讨论的是 SageMaker 所以重点谈谈 SageMaker
Now, automating the infrastructure was not the whole job.
自动化整个流程并不够
Like the job is not done if you just automating infrastructure,
如果只是自动化这些流程 工作并没有完成
because you still have people that are not
因为还有些人
particularly very familiar with machine learning algorithms.
并非很熟悉机器学习算法
So what we decided to do is to bring in the most popular, the most common,
所以我们决定加入最热门 最常见
the most useful machine learning algorithms that exist out there [inaudible] is one
最有用的机器学习算法
of the competitions winning machine learning algorithm nowadays,
包括如今赢得各种比赛的机器学习算法
some computer vision algorithms,
一些计算机视觉算法
principal component analysis, KMeans,
主成分分析 K 均值
k nearest neighbor, linear regression,
k 最近邻 线性回归
logistic regression, Multiclass classification.
逻辑回归 多类别分类算法
So you're probably your familiar with these names,
如果你研究过机器学习
if you've played around with machine learning.
应该就熟悉这些名称
So what we set off to do as a challenge is to essentially take these algorithms,
我们迎接挑战 针对大型数据集
optimize them for large-scale,
优化这些算法
for large datasets, and then make them available in Amazon SageMaker.
并将它们内置到 Amazon SageMaker 中
The other thing that we decided to do,
另一方面
is to go to our internal team at Amazon and say, hey,
我们询问 Amazon 内部团队
what are the cool algorithms that you guys are working on at the moment?
“你们目前正在研发的是哪些精彩算法？”
So we got some nuggets from there an algorithm like BlazingText,
我们根据这些反馈开发了 BlazingText
which is an improvement on Word2vec that essentially,
BlazingText 是 Word2vec 的优化版本
we use that internal Amazon to build word embeddings,
并在 Amazon 内部构建字词嵌入
like to build embeddings of products,
例如产品 广告内容
ad items, of user comments, and things like that.
用户评论等嵌入
So we get that from the team and then package that put that in SageMaker.
我们根据内部团队的反馈创建相关工具 并将工具内置到 SageMaker 中
So when you embark on a journey of not just making
当我们不仅会打造平台和服务
platforms and services but also algorithms available to people,
而且向开发人员提供算法时
I think a very natural thing to do is to
很自然地
also put examples around those algorithms to make sure that
就需要围绕这些算法提供示例
people can use these algorithms with lower friction of of entry.
使大家能够很快上手使用这些算法
So then we decided to build a lot of examples around, initially,
所以我们决定提供大量算法示例
these algorithms, but also people got super excited,
但是大家变得很激动
and then it just started contributing to this example.
开始贡献更多示例
So we ended up eventually,
最终获得了
with more than 30,
超过 30 个示例
and it's probably a lot more now Jupyter Notebooks that we open source,
现在的 Jupyter Notebook 比一开始的开源项目多了很多
and that are also available within SageMaker.
并且内置到了 SageMaker 中
So the idea there was to make sure that if
我们希望
a data scientist and/or developer wants to use SageMaker,
数据科学家/开发人员在决定使用 SageMaker 时
they can jump on the platform,
能够立即使用该平台
not just have access to the infrastructure and all the automation,
不仅仅可以访问基础工具以及自动化工具
but also have access to,
而且可以查看示例
essentially an example that can get them through building, training, deploying, hosting,
了解如何从头到尾地构建 训练
tuning machine learning models end-to-end,
部署 托管和优化机器学习模型
and we wanted to make sure that everything is available there including some sample data.
我们希望提供所有的资源 包括示例数据
So that was the entire idea.
这就是我们的初衷
It started as a small project and it grew because people started contributing,
一开始只是很小的项目 但是随着人们的贡献 变得越来越庞大
and we also enable our external customers to
并且我们还请外部客户
contribute to that library which is available on GitHub.
在 GitHub 代码库中贡献代码
It's an ecosystem that is growing pretty large around that,
这个生态系统发展的越来越庞大
and that's one of the things I'm also very proud of
我对此感到很骄傲
Yes. I think it's an amazing resource,
是的是很强大的资源
and I was thinking like,
我认为
with especially the use of Jupyter Notebooks,
尤其对 Jupyter Notebook 的使用
it really ties into what we try to do at Udacity with education.
与优达学城的教育方式很像
it's like, a question of how do you make this the
如何让学员能访问这些资源
most accessible by creating a sort of framing,
打造一种学习环境
that allows people to really focus on
使学员能够专注于
whatever machine learning problem they're trying to solve,
他们要解决的机器学习问题
whether it's something data or something with an algorithm,
包括数据和算法问题
reducing any extraneous information there,
减少无关的信息
and allowing them to explore and play around with these.
让学员能够探索和尝试这些问题
I think there's something really powerful.
我认为这些很有用
Yes. People learn by doing.
是的实践是最好的学习途径
So if it is possible for you to,
在学完 K 均值
after learning about KMeans or k nearest neighbor algorithms,
或 k 最近邻等算法之后
find a way to implement that right away, in a matter of,
如果能够快速应用算法
I don't know, 10-15 minutes by just following instructions, it becomes real.
例如在 10-15 分钟之后跟着说明操作 就会牢牢记住这些知识
Then you can eventually, deploy that in web surveys or something like that,
最终能够在网络中部署这些算法
and then you use the product.
并使用产品
So I think the ability to bring that association with
我认为利用示例
an example that guides the learners is very useful,
指导学习者很重要
and yes, we're seeing a lot of momentum around that capability.
我们发现这些工具的应用势头很强